Drama Spirit
Come out quickly.
I need to talk to you.
Forget about saving the herb for now.
What do you want?
This Ephemeral Frost Herb...
can indeed cure the Five-Fold Poison Herb's toxin.
Right?
Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
If this Ephemeral Frost Herb doesn't bloom,
it's no different from a weed.
Eldest Cousin.
I just saw Carpenter Li
when the poison took effect.
It was truly a fate worse than death.
This time, listen to me.
Let's hurry back to the capital.
Have His Majesty summon the best doctors for you.
No need.
But...
Where did you find the Ephemeral Frost Herb?
In the miasma forest.
Think carefully about the exact spot.
Maybe I can think of a way to make it bloom.
The exact spot...
was under a withered ginkgo tree.
A ginkgo tree...
Let me think of another way.
Eldest Cousin.
About you being poisoned...
You really won't tell A Lan?
She doesn't need to know.
Zixiu.
You must help me keep this secret.
Please bless us.
Let's go check it out.
Bless us.
Please bless us.
Bless us, bless us.
What are they doing?
The matter of my young master seeking test subjects
has spread throughout the city.
Everyone is terrified.
Today happens to be a day for prayers.
Everyone is thinking of going to Tianyin Temple to pray.
Second Master Luo was taken by Pan Yu.
Second Master Luo's death is no loss.
I'm just afraid Pan Yu
will take his anger out on Tianyin City's innocent people.
Let's go to Tianyin Temple.
Eldest Cousin.
But your poison...
It's fine.
Tell A Lan
we're going to Tianyin Temple.
Yes, Young Master.
Let's go.
Murder!
Open the door! Open up!
Darn it!
This door can only be opened from the other side.
What do we do?
Murder! Murder!
Run!
Young Master Pan.
You must stop this.
Siqing's poison took effect last night.
She hasn't woken up yet.
She won't last the day.
None of this has anything to do with the city's people.
Don't harm the innocent.
Siqing, like you,
cared for the city's people.
But who will pity her?
She loved Tianyin City.
She loved the people here.
Fine.
Then I'll have them...
have them all accompany her to the grave.
Help!
Open the door!
Open up!
After they're all dead,
I'll go down to join her.
That way, she won't be too lonely.
Zixiu.
Protect the people.
Understood.
Eldest Cousin! Brother!
You're poisoned with the Five-Fold Poison Herb.
How could you possibly be a match for me?
I've tried every possible method.
What exactly have I missed?
But I can only give you one hint.
Far away in the horizon,
yet right before your eyes.
Yuwen Rui said
he found it under a withered ginkgo tree.
Could it be...?
It all depends on this.
It's no use!
Where are they?
That's right.
They went to Tianyin Temple.
They asked me to tell you.
A Zi.
Seventh Cousin.
Zixiu.
A Zi.
Seventh Cousin.
I'm fine.
How could you possibly be fine?
Really, don't worry.
Siqing doesn't have much time left.
Then I'll have you pave her way to the underworld.
Open the door!
Lord Grand Secretary.
You can't protect them.
I don't want to kill you.
Enough talk.
Then I'm sorry.
Eldest Cousin!
Stop!
A Lan.
Fourth Sister.
Are you alright?
Young Master Pan, do you still wish to save Miss Lin?
This Ephemeral Frost Herb in my hand
can cure the Five-Fold Poison Herb's toxin.
A single white flower?
Miss A Lan, are you trying to fool me?
If it were just an ordinary white flower,
why would I go to such lengths to find it?
Well?
Go quickly.
You're poisoned.
You... you tested the medicine for me?
I will definitely save you.
Young Master Pan
In this world
the only thing that can cure the Five-Fold Poison Herb
is the Ephemeral Frost Herb in my hand.
How can I trust you?
Believe it or not.
But Miss Lin
probably can't wait for you to hesitate any longer.
Fine.
I'll trust you this once.
One Ephemeral Frost Herb cannot fully cure the poison.
How to find the Ephemeral Frost Herb
and how to make it bloom
are known only to me.
To completely cure the Five-Fold Poison Herb's toxin,
one must take the antidote for forty-nine consecutive days.
What do you want?
I can give you the Ephemeral Frost Herb.
But you must promise me
that after you refine the antidote today,
aside from Miss Lin's portion,
you must give the remainder to me.
Then I will tell you how to find the Ephemeral Frost Herb.
Alright.
No problem.
If I don't receive the antidote today,
you'll never find a second herb in your lifetime.
If I can't save Siqing,
none of you will leave Tianyin City alive.
Yuwen Rui!
How is Eldest Cousin?
And Seventh Cousin?
His wound has been bandaged.
He just needs to rest well for a few days.
That Ephemeral Frost Herb...
Can it really cure the Five-Fold Poison Herb?
Most likely.
It's just unknown if Pan Yu
can successfully refine the antidote.
I'll have someone prepare medicine for Eldest Cousin.
Don't think that because you did this,
I'll be grateful to you.
If Pan Yu fails to refine the antidote...
If you...
Then I'll resent you for life.
I'll never forgive you, even unto death.
Who told you to take it upon yourself to test some medicine for me?
And what's this about sending a message to Father Emperor
to cancel the marriage arrangement?
If you're okay,
this time,
I won't hold it against you.
Royal Sister...
What time is it?
It's midnight.
Midnight...
Pan Yu still hasn't delivered the antidote.
Could the antidote refinement have failed?
Yuwen Rui!
I'll go find a doctor!
How are you feeling?
I didn't tell you
because I was afraid you'd be like this.
About testing the medicine for you...
If anything happens to you,
I will absolutely never forgive you, you know that?
As long as you're okay,
I'll be fine no matter what.
Listen to me.
Right now,
leave Tianyin City immediately.
Live well.
But if I...
No!
You won't be in danger.
You won't be in danger!
A Zi...
Let me help you.
Here.
Where are Big Brother and the others?
They went to see Pan Yu.
It's fine.
It'll be completely healed in a few days.
Does it hurt a lot?
No, it doesn't hurt.
When you fought Pan Yu,
why did you take the sword strike for me?
I...
I didn't think that much at the time.
Seventh Cousin...
You like me too,
right?
I...
You do like me!
A Zi...
You are the noble Fourth Princess of Yunmi.
And I...
I'm just a member of the Yuwen family,
a good-for-nothing playboy with no ambition.
Why worry about all that?
You like me.
I like you too.
That's enough.
I'm afraid you'll regret it in the future.
Being with the one you love,
what is there to regret?
Thank you for finding the Ephemeral Frost Herb
and saving my life.
It's nothing.
Fortunately, no innocent citizens died because of you.
Otherwise, this official wouldn't let you leave so easily.
It was my mistake.
From now on, I will travel the world with Siqing,
healing the sick and saving lives.
I will not harbor thoughts of killing again.
If you break your word...
Rest assured.
I, Pan Yu, am a man of my word.
It's Miss A Lan who is full of lies.
She actually tricked me, saying
the antidote must be taken for forty-nine days.
If I hadn't said that,
what if you refined the antidote
and didn't give it to me?
Since it's an immortal herb,
naturally there's only this one.
That thing is useless for you to keep.
But it's useful for them.
So give it to them.
The secret of the Map of the Nine Provinces
was known only to the leader of Shadow Gate.
Before his death, he hid the treasure map's secret
within Shadow Gate's forbidden sanctuary.
Where is this sanctuary?
I only know it's in Luojing.
The exact location
you'll have to find for yourselves.
This key can open the sanctuary,
but three keys are required.
Before the leader died,
he entrusted the three keys separately to me,
the Lute Fanatic, and the Sword Fanatic.
The Lute Fanatic is currently hiding in Dongyang City.
The Sword Fanatic, however, has no fixed abode.
Love Fanatic?
Lute Fanatic.
Shadow Gate isn't very particular with names, is it?
What if someone mispronounces the nasal sounds?
The flower has been used to make the antidote.
All that remains is this.
Since this Ephemeral Frost Herb is so unique,
take good care of it.
It might bloom again someday.
Then let's go.
Farewell.
We should go too.
You rest well first.
I'll have the kitchen prepare some food for you.
I'm not hungry.
Stay with me a little longer.
From now on,
I will never push you away again.
Young Master Zixiu.
Enter.
Young Master.
Is your wound feeling better?
Miss A Zi.
I came to ask you something.
Go ahead.
My young master...
Will he ever return to Ren'an Hall?
Of course.
After all that has happened,
how could Miss Lin be willing
to stay in Tianyin City?
In my heart,
both my master and Miss Lin are good people.
If not for how Second Master Luo and the others treated Miss Lin,
my master wouldn't have...
Fortunately, Miss Lin was cured.
Yes.
Young Master.
You should rest properly first.
I'll take my leave now.
Shadow Gate's Yun Shang is indeed as the rumors say:
he loves his wife more than life itself.
But I can understand him.
If you were ever not by my side,
I'm afraid I'd be even more frantic than him.
Don't worry.
I won't leave you.
It's already like this.
Can it still survive?
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
Go.
After them!
Lord Grand Secretary.
Your serious injury hasn't healed.
You're probably no match for us.
Who sent you?
What did Shadow Gate's Yun Shang tell you?
The brocade box he gave you...
does it relate to the secret of the Map of the Nine Provinces?
If you tell me everything truthfully,
perhaps I can spare both your lives.
You think you can?
Attack!
Yuwen Rui!
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Go find the Master.
Let's go.
The mysterious person has been quiet all along
just waiting for today.
The assassins think they've found
a clue to decipher the treasure map.
They'll report to the mysterious person immediately.
They'd never expect
we already have agents secretly following them.
You just fought the assassins
and fell into the water.
Are your injuries really okay?
So worried about me?
Who's worried about you?
I was just thinking,
if you collapse here,
I'd have to struggle to get you back to Ren'an Hall.
What's wrong?
Did your wound reopen?
Let's go.
Careful!
Master.
The contents of this brocade box
must be the key to unlocking
the secret on the Map of the Nine Provinces.
What about Yuwen Rui and the others?
They fell off the cliff.
Their chances of survival are slim.
He's not that easy to kill.
Go investigate.
Find out what's really inside this box.
Yes.
By the way,
Master.
This medicine will help your wound heal.
Who's there?
Yuwen Rui!
How are you?
Don't scare me!
A Lan.
I'm here.
I...
I'm okay.
Yuwen Rui!
Yuwen Rui, wake up!
Don't die!
Yuwen Rui!
Didn't you say...
didn't you say you liked me?
I actually like you too.
As long as you wake up,
as long as you wake up,
I... I'll promise you anything, really.
I'll promise you anything.
You said it.
Was it fun tricking me?
I just wanted to hear your true feelings.
You just said
you like me too.
And you'd promise me anything.
Who said that?
How could I possibly say
such nauseating words?
Are you feverish?
Delirious from the fever?
You were in such pain earlier.
Was that also an illusion?
That was no illusion.
Just now, I...
was genuinely quite upset.
I was thinking at the time,
we're in this desolate wilderness.
If you were to die,
a poor, helpless woman like me,
how would I ever get back?
Take off your clothes.
Why should I take them off?
My clothes are already dry.
Wear mine.
Why is this robe so big?
The sleeves are so long.
The hem is too.
It's such a hassle to put on.
With all this chatter, do you need my help?
No.
Thank you.
Where's the belt?
I don't see it.
I forgot to give it to you.
A man's belt is rather intricate.
Let me help you.
Too tight?
Hurry up.
There.
I wonder if your men
tracking the assassins found anything.
Chen Liang is most skilled in tracking.
If he discovers anything,
he will come find me.
The person tailing you was surely arranged by Yuwen Rui.
It seems obtaining the brocade box
was merely one part of his plan.
The item inside the box was also a fake.
Yuwen Rui is truly cunning and deep.
Fortunately, our master was vigilant.
He was not discovered by them.
From now on, Yuwen Rui will surely be more alert.
For now, we must not act rashly.
Understood.
He's quite pleasing to look at, isn't he?
Why did you stop looking?
I saw your face was dirty.
I wanted to wipe it for you.
All clean now.
My lord.
Well?
Did you see who the mysterious person was?
My lord.
I have failed.
I was detected by the other party.
I could not see his true face.
I only know he seemed to be injured.
Injured?
Yes.
I also found this.
Did you find out what medicine this is?
It's a miraculous medicine for treating external wounds.
Nothing else was discovered.
Our master's injury is not serious, is it?
It's nothing.
Right.
I haven't given you the medicine yet.
The medicine is gone.
Oh no.
That medicine was specially made.
If I remember correctly,
the bottle's base should be carved with a stag antler totem.
What did you say?